{
    "subject": "resource/Songs_in_the_Dark_(album)",
    "predicate": "property/artist",
    "object": "the Wainwright Sisters",
    "human_readable": "The artist of Songs in the Dark album is the Wainwright Sisters.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8956221342086792,
            "question": "What is the name of the album by the Wainwright Sisters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8802297711372375,
            "question": "Which album was created by the Wainwright Sisters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8258699774742126,
            "question": "Name a musical album created by the Wainwright Sisters."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7924904227256775,
            "question": "Can you tell me the name of an album by the Wainwright Sisters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7515735030174255,
            "question": "Who are the artists behind the album 'Songs in the Dark'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7366780042648315,
            "question": "Is 'Songs in the Dark' an album?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6557433605194092,
            "question": "Who created the album 'Songs in the Dark'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5171425938606262,
            "question": "What musical work is associated with the Wainwright Sisters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47163110971450806,
            "question": "The Wainwright Sisters are known for which musical work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4312678277492523,
            "question": "What is the name of the musical group behind the album 'Songs in the Dark'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The artist of Songs in the Dark album is the Wainwright Sisters.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2517_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Wainwright Sisters are known for which musical work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2517_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What musical work is associated with the Wainwright Sisters?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2517_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who created the album 'Songs in the Dark'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2517_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2517_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2517_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2517_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2517_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2517_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2517_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2517_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2517_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2517_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2517_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents support that the artist of the Songs in the Dark album is indeed the Wainwright Sisters, as stated in multiple articles and track listings."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that \"Songs in the Dark\" is an album by the Wainwright Sisters, specifically mentioning Martha Wainwright and Lucy Wainwright Roche as the members of this duo. Therefore, the triple stating that the artist of the \"Songs in the Dark\" album is the Wainwright Sisters is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}